# Rosdyana Kusuma (郭祿丁)

# Research Assistance - Developer

Taoyuan | 0974-121-306 | rosdyana.kusuma@gmail.com

### **Summary**

**Research Assistance**, currently focuses on the implementation of Machine Learning in Bioinformatic and financial data. Has more than four years experiences as **Developer** on game development in Gameloft (Indonesia branch) which is help me on developing my technical and soft skills. Currently, working as paid internship developer in Omniscient Cloud Technology.

# Work experience

Intern. Developer

2017 - Current

## Omniscient Cloud Technology Inc. Taiwan

As a Intern. developer in Omniscient Cloud Technology Inc., I have some tasks from my supervisor related to build Machine Learning model through data analyzing and android application development.

#### Programmer Supervisor

2014 - 2016

#### Gameloft Indonesia

Leading a team to port the game for Windows platform (Windows 8/8.1/10, Windows Mobile).

- Work together with the Game producer to make sure the project finish on-time and tackle some difficulty.
- Work together with Creation team in other studio production to catch-up project progress.
- Has a responsibility to manage human resources, both technically and personally.
- Identify and analyze the problem before giving suggestion to team members.
- Organizing and monitoring technical and soft skill of team members.
- Maintenance daily scrum.
- Maintenance weekly training for the team member to build their skills.
- Advance level of some programming languages.

Platform: Windows OS PC, Windows Phone

#### Programmer

2012 - 2014

#### Gameloft Indonesia

As a programmer in porting team, I need to follow rules and order from my supervisor.

- Basic level of some programming languages.
- Has specific role in the team.
- Has responsibility to daily tasks.
- Has responsibility for daily report.

During my career as programmer, I was a specific programmer for game optimization and maintenance game server.

Platform : Android

Skills

Python Programming

C++ Programming

C# Programming

R Programming

JAVA Programming

Game Development

Irrlicht Engine, Unity, OGRE3D

Android Development

Web Development

NodeJs, PHP, HTML, CSS, Javascript

Database

MySQL, MongoDB

Networking

# **Education**

Master Degree 2016 - Current

Yuan Ze University - Taiwan

Department of Computer Science and Engineering

Bachelor Degree 2008 - 2012

AMIKOM University - Indonesia

Department of Engineering informatics